Walter and Martha Leuba Prints SC.1988.02
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Known Artists, I.
  - Renton, Michael
    - Prints, 1965
      - R.A. Brimmell, 1965; (5 3/4 x 5")
        Wood engraving proof
  - Rewald, Dr. John
    - Prints
      - Man and ideas, (7 1/2 x 5")
  - Reyers, W.L.
    - Prints
      - Polar bear, (10 3/4 x 7")
        Signed woodcut with foxing
  - Reynolds, Sir Joshua
    - Prints
      - David Garrick, (5 1/2 x 3 1/2")
      - James Bosnell, (5 1/8 x 3 13/16")
  - Rhodes, Cecil
    - Prints
      - The Forefathers, (19 x 8 1/4")
      - The Schoolboy, (17 x 7 1/2")
  - Rice, Bernard
    - Prints
      - Bonsien village, (9 1/4 x 6 1/2")
        Signed wood engraving, 1/50
  - Rice, James
    - Prints
      - Joachim du Bellay, (9 3/8 x 6 3/8")
        Poem
  - Richard, Seewald
    - Prints
      - Zwanzig holzchnitte zu den hirtengedichten
  - Richardson, H.B.
    - Prints
      - Hardrian's wall and castle nick milecastle, (6 1/4 x 8 5/8")
  - Richmond, George
    - Prints
      - Sara Colerdige, (5 1/4 x 3 15/16")
      - Sara Coleridge's daughter Edith, (5 5/16 x 3 15/16")
  - Robbia, Luca della
    - Prints
      - Madonna, (5 7/16 x 3 5/8")
  - Rooke, Noel
    - Prints
      - Subject: Abstract mountain landscape, (8 x 11")
  - Rosenbach, A.S.W.
    - Prints
      - After love, (6 x 3 7/8")
  - Ross, John
    - Prints, 1962
      - Provincetown beach, 1962; (26 1/2 x 19 3/4")
        Signed and matted multicolor wodcut, 27/100
  - Ross, Vera
    - Prints
      - Phantasy, (7 3/4 x 5 3/8")
        Signed wood engraving with considerable foxing
  - Rothenstein, William
    - Prints
      - To truth alone obedience, (4 x 3 5/16")
  - Rounds, Glen
    - Prints
      - The blind colt, (9 3/4 x 14 3/4")
  - Rowlandson
    - Prints
      - Dr. Syntax and bookseller, (11 1/2 x 8 1/2")
        Framed water color etching
      - Peter Plumb's diary, (15 3/4 x 10 1/2")
        Signed hand colored etching
      - Three principal reqisites to form a modern man of fashion, (15 1/2 x 10 1/2")
  - Rozendaal, J.W.
    - Prints, 1954
      - Three moving figures, 1954; (20 x 15 1/4")
        Signed linocut with relief plate, 44/200
  - Rudolph, Wilhelm
    - Prints
      - Ferry, (11 3/4 x 16")
        Woodcut reproduction
  - Rutherson, Albert
    - Prints
      - Journey's end, (17 x 7 3/8")
  - Takabatake
    - Prints
      - Subject: 4 figures with one holding violin, (7 1/4 x 9 1/2")
        Signed pen and ink linocut
  - Takeda, Sadayuki
    - Prints, 1964
      - Tea house, 1964; (21 x 18")
        Signed and matted woodblock print, 147/210
  - Tanner, H.S.
    - Prints, 1840
      - A New map of Pennsylvania, 1840; (15 1/2 x 13")
        Hand colored wood engraving
  - Thackeray, W.M.
    - Prints
      - Mrs. Brookfield, (4 7/16 x 2 13/16")
  - Madsen-Conant, Patricia Carol, 1939
    - Prints
      - The General, (16 1/8 x 11 1/4")
      - Symbols, (15 x 9 1/4")
  - Thomas, J.
    - Prints
      - William Roscoe, ( 6 7/8 x 4 3/4")
    - Townsend, J. Barton
      - Prints
        - Haec generi incrementa fides, (4 1/4 x 3")
  - Trofimov, Victor
    - Prints
      - Subject: Tiger, (13 1/4 x 22 1/4")
        Signed multicolor linocut
  - Trump, James D.
    - Prints, 1966
      - September solstice, 1966; (7 7/8 x 5 3/8")
  - Tuke, Samuel
    - Prints
      - Roman West Gate, Lincoln, (6 1/4 x 8 5/8")
        Lithograph
  - Turner, J.M.W.
    - Prints
      - Hurstmonceux Castle, Sussex, (6 1/4 x 8 5/8")
  - Tufiño, Rafael, 1922-2008
    - Prints
      - Concurso de tiples y cuatros, (Image: 19 x 31")
        Signed and matted silkscreen poster
  - Tyler, Edwards
    - Prints
      - The Visions of Mary, (4 3/4 x 6 1/2")
        Wooden gravings
  - Uboda, F.
    - Prints
      - White dream, (19 1/2 x 26")
        Signed and matted woodcut, 107/200
  - Uchima, Ansei, 1921-2000
    - Prints, 1961-1963
      - By the lake, 1961; (14 3/4 x 22 1/2")
        Signed and matted colored woodcut, 70/200
      - Descending moon, 1963; (8 1/2 x 20")
        Sigend and matted colored woodcut, 193/200
      - Joy, (16 3/4 x 22 1/2")
        Signed and matted multicolor woodblock print, 76/200
      - Summer stream, 1962; (22 1/2 x 17 1/2")
        Signed and matted multicolor woodcut, 116/200
  - Ueda, Fujo, 1899-?
    - Prints, 1966
      - The Garden of the temple in Kyoto, 1966; (Image: 18 x 12 3/4")
        Signed and matted woodblock, 40/120
  - Unwin, Francis Sydney
    - Prints
      - Village on waterfront, (9 x 5 3/4")
        Signed etching
  - Unwin, Nora S.
    - Prints, 1951
      - Warm afternoon, 1951; (11 x 7")
      - Convolvulus, (6 3/4 x 8 1/4")
      - Teazer and grasses, (6 1/2 x 8 1/2")
  - Urejweiss
    - Prints
      - Berg-flockenblume/frauenschuh, (11 x 15")
        Sigend and matted handcolored lithograph, number six of series
      - Fruhlings-enzian/zwerg-buchs/schneeheide, (11 x 15")
        Signed and matted handcolored lithograph, number seven of series
      - Scheuchzers glockenblume/silberwurz, (11 x 15")
        Signed and matted handcolored lithograph, number fourteen of series
      - Felsen-ehrenpreis/alpen-petersbart, berg-nelkenwurz, geschnabeltes lausekraut, (11 x 15")
        Signed and matted handcolored lithograph, number fifteen of series
      - Hasenlattich, (11 x 15")
        Signed and matted handcolored lithograph, number eighteen of series
      - Vielblattriges lausekraut/runde teufelskralle, (11 x 15")
        Signed and matted handcolored lithograph, number twenty-four of series
      - Getupfelter enzian, (11 x 15")
        Signed and matted handcolored lithograph, number thirty-five of series
      - Alpen-rispengrass, allermannsharnisch, (11 x 15")
        Signed and matted handcolored lithograph, number thirty-six of series
      - Alpen-mannstreu, (11 x 15")
        Signed and matted handcolored lithograph, number forty-two of series
  - Utamaro
    - Prints
      - Showing a tattoo, (10 x 15")
        Signed reprint of a woodblock print
  - Vertue, George, 1684-1756
    - Prints
      - Thomas Sackville, Earl of Dorset, 1737
- Unknown Artists, II.
- Postcards?, III.